(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
[dishes rattling]
[Heeju] I wanted to run away
from the pawn shop.
But there was a shadow of misfortune
that fell on my shoulders.
It was a weight
that I just couldn't shake off.
[gasps]
[flies buzzing]
[creaking]
[inhales and exhales sharply]
[Cheoljung] Do you know
how worried I've been?
You've got a perfectly good home.
Why are you putting yourself through this?
Oh, no! Mm!
[Cheoljung] Look at you.
Your poor hands.
Whatever. Can you just go now?
[exhales]
'Kay, I'll go.
[Cheoljung] But you should
come home more often.
We can all have dinner together, yeah?
[inhales on cigarette]
Gross. That bastard.
[Heeju] I swore to myself I would never
be lured by that light that got my mother.
I needed a light of my own.
One that would hide me from my shadow.
But without money,
you don't have a lot of options.
[roulette wheel rattling]
[Heeju] Gold Land makes promises
of dazzling fortune.
But that's not what I dreamed of.
Maybe all I wanted was just some guarantee
that I could be safe here.
It was all someone like me could hope for.
[indistinct chatter]
[chips clinking]
[Male Gambler] Hey, hey, hey, hey.
-What's the deal with these red ones?
-[Heeju] Sorry?
They're all supposed to be yellow.
I exchanged them for yellow!
Ch-change it!
Hey! Hear me or what?
-[Guard A] All right, that's enough.
-Do you think I'm stupid, bitch?
-[Guard A] Time to go, sir.
-[Guard B] Let's go.
[Male Gambler] Let go of me!
Get your hands off me!
-Call the manager! Call the manager now!
-[Guard A] Get him out. Let's go!
[Dokyung] What the hell?
What's up with that guy?
Oh.
100 gold chips, please.
[Heeju] That's when he walked
into my life.
A man who seemed to be made
of nothing but good luck.
He was like a mirage
that came out of nowhere.
Something that didn't belong in my world.
As if he'd disappear if I touched him.
Time to see if luck is on
my side today.
[Dokyung] Thank you, Miss Heeju.
STYLE
::cue()
[Dokyung] I bought this on my way back
from Hong Kong. It's for you.
Heard you like planes, so...
Uh, 100 gold chips, please.
[machine rattling]
[Dokyung exhales sharply]
Time to see if luck is on my side today.
Thank you.
[Dokyung exhaling]
[Dokyung] Whew!
[all gasping and laughing]
[woman gasps]
Yes!
[crowd cheering]
[applause]
[Woman] Did you see that?
[Dokyung breathing heavily]
Hey, see this?
It's yours Heeju.
I only won it because of you.
[scoffs]
[exhales]
Uh...
[indistinct chatter]
[Cheoljung inhales deeply]
Give me some gold chips,
why don't ya?
This is where you were hiding, huh?
[Cheoljung] Do you have any idea
how long I've been looking for you?
[Heeju] Get out.
I don't have anything to say to you.
That's no way to talk to your uncle.
Like it or not,
the two of us are family, ya know.
You are not my family.
Hmm.
But you're my sweet little niece.
[hiccups and grunts]
Enough of this.
Let's just go home now.
Did my aunt tell you, then?
Where to find me?
[Cheoljung] Of course.
She was worried sick.
[Cheoljung] You're her only niece.
Come back home now, really.
Heeju.
-[Cheoljung] Do you really think...
-Security, he's drunk.
...you can live in Jeongsan
without me finding out about it?
-[Guard A] Let's go, let's go.
-[Cheoljung] Come on.
[Cheoljung] I'm this girl's uncle, okay?
Ah, shitheads!
Get the hell off of me!
[Cheoljung] She's my niece!
I'm telling you!
-[Guard B] Come on!
-Be sure to eat well, okay?
-[Cheoljung] You've lost weight, you know!
-[Heeju] Even the light of this place
-couldn't conceal my shadow.
-[Cheoljung] I'll be back for you! Heeju!
STYLE
::cue()
HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
[Heeju] How much longer could I endure?
Like my mother...
...I was already starting to wither.
I felt like I couldn't go on much longer.
I had to reach for it.
Even if it was just
a mirage that would disappear.
[♪ sad music]
[door lock beeps]
[door opens]
Heeju.
Here you go.
I exchanged those chips you gave me
into cash for you.
[inhales sharply]
Uh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it that way.
What did you mean, then?
Well, either way it was up to you
to decide whether to come here or not.
[Dokyung] But take this at least.
As a token of my appreciation.
[grunts]
[Heeju] This is everything I have.
Take the money and place
a single bet for me.
[Heeju] I've decided to trust you.
And for once in my life...
...take a gamble and see if my life
has any luck at all.
[Female Dealer] The game at table two
will start in one minute.
[Female Dealer] You have one minute
if you want to play.
[crowd cheering]
[Dokyung] Congrats, Heeju.
Good job.
You won.
The pot is all yours.
[chips rattling]
[Heeju exhales]
Wait a sec, Heeju.
Just a sec.
-[Heeju gasping]
-It's okay.
-[Dokyung] It's okay.
-[Heeju] Wait. I don't...
Let's place these ones on top.
What?
Trust me, Heeju.
[♪ hopeful music]
[Heeju exhales]
[Dokyung exhales]
[Heeju sighs]
[crowd whispering]
[both exhale]
Ten.
[Heeju exhales]
[Dokyung] Okay.
[cheers and applause]
[Heeju gasps]
Heeju! Heeju, you did it!
You won it all!
[Dokyung] Okay, these are yours.
[Heeju gasps]
This is enough, right?
Congratulations.
[Heeju] From then on,
for the first time in my life,
it finally felt like there
was a light in my world.
Like I was seeing the sun
for the first time
after coming out of a dark tunnel.
It was warm and everything around me
was crystal clear.
-Come here.
-What?
[Heeju] Every moment,
every day filled with gratitude.
I was happy.
What, you don't like mine?
What's not to like?
[indistinct chatter]
STYLE
::cue()
[Dokyung] What are you staring at?
[Heeju] Am I really allowed
to live like this?
[Dokyung] What does that mean?
Just like this.
Like other people.
Happy and calm.
You met me,
so you must be lucky.
[chuckles]
You're the first person
to ever say that to me.
Ever since I was a kid,
everyone always told me I
was an unlucky little brat.
[Heeju] And it was kind of true.
So none of this feels real.
Being happy like this.
Being with you.
[inhales and exhales sharply]
Isn't happiness meant for everyone?
Mm.
[Dokyung] You don't have
to worry about anything now.
Just trust me and follow my lead.
This is barely the beginning.
[Dokyung] From this moment on...
...I'm gonna show you exactly
how lucky you are.
Santé?
[exhales]
Santé.
[glasses clink]
[distant seagulls cawing]
[Heeju giggles]
NO ENTRY
[♪ suspenseful music]
[grunts]
[Heeju] Is this mine?
No.
Then is it Lee Dokyung's?
Also no.
I don't know whose it is.
Maybe I don't wanna know.
But if it doesn't belong
to anyone anyway,
why shouldn't I take it?
At least,
that's what I kept telling myself.
You're just doing what Lee Dokyung
told you to do.
You can't help it because you love him.
That's what you think, right?
Did I really love Lee Dokyung?
Or was it that I just wanted to escape?
Did it really matter?
No, but now I have
to decide for myself.
What does it really mean to be happy?
[inhales and exhales sharply]
[♪ sad piano music]
[♪ music continues]
STYLE
::cue()
EPISODE 4
HIM
[Jinman] Stop bugging me about it, okay?
I'll find it soon.
[indistinct chatter]
Yes, I know that.
The chairman will be back next week?
[Jinman] I'll get back
to you as soon as I can.
Yeah.
[exhales]
[Jinman] Oh! Ah!
Ah, fuck me.
Seriously?
[indistinct chatter]
Ah, shit.
[mouse wheel scrolling]
Is that a woman?
WITNESS STATEMENT RECORD
WITNESS PERSONAL INFORMATION
[Male Detective] And your name?
[Sunok] Yeo Sunok.
[Male Detective exhales sharply]
[Male Detective] Around what time
did this happen?
Um...
[Sunok] Last night.
Around 10:00.
[Male Detective] Okay, around 10:00 p.m.
Afternoon, sir.
-Wait!
-Yeah?
Well, that woman.
[Jinman] What's her deal?
Ah, her?
She was booked this morning
at a local precinct,
but they handed it over to us.
She bashed her husband with a golf club.
He's in the hospital.
Her husband reported it?
No, she reported it herself.
[Jinman] What about the husband?
He wants to press charges.
According to him, she-
she was after his pawnshop's money.
-Says he has evidence.
-[Mija] Sunok!
Sunok! What's going on here?
Is it true?
-Well, I'll be going.
-[grunts]
-You didn't really do it, did you?
-Hi, there.
[Male Detective]
Are you a family member?
No, but she's like a sister.
How did you find out?
What are you saying?
You called me to come and get you.
Can you make sure she leaves?
Sunok, dammit,
that's not what should concern you.
[Mija] You shouldn't be here.
[Mija] Detective, this woman
is very sick.
She has terminal cancer.
[Mija] I mean, she should be in
the hospital, not in a place like this!
[Male Detective] I understand, but I
still have to continue processing her.
-Detective, please!
-Jeongsan-gun.
-Sunok!
-Five, dash, 18 Bukju.
Detective!
SAMJEON JEWELRY DEPARTMENT STORE
[Woogy] Ah, okay.
No, no, no, no.
Excuse me.
Yeah, sure thing.
Thank you. Mm.
[inhales sharply]
We could have made preparations
if you had called ahead of time.
[Male Store Owner] Sorry about that.
But we'll buy the gold bar.
We'll have the cash ready soon.
[Male Store Owner] Do you mind waiting
a little longer?
Of course.
[chuckles]
[exhales]
Uh, sir. Excuse me.
This one here.
Can I buy this?
Uh, would you like to look
at that one, too?
-Heh, yeah.
-Sure. Just one minute.
[Female Store Owner] You want it in cash?
130 million?
Yeah.
[exhale sharply]
If you can't do it, don't worry.
-I'll go somewhere else.
-Oh, no, no, no, no.
[chuckles nervously]
Wait just a minute.
[exhales]
[Female Customer] Honey, I want this one!
-Isn't it beautiful?
-Really?
You don't want this one?
It's shiny.
Happy with that little thing?
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
You don't want to count to make sure?
I plan on doing more business with you,
so I'm sure it's the right amount.
Ah, yes.
[inhales sharply]
TRANSFEREE: KIM MINCHEOL
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
KIM MINCHEOL
STYLE
::cue()
JEWELRY WORLD
[cell phone vibrating]
Heeju, what's up?
[Heeju] Where are you?
Where do you think? Daejeong.
Just finishing up with the potatoes.
Where are you?
You don't need to know.
I need you to just show me where you
are right now.
[Woogy] Ah, why can't you just trust me?
See? Jewelry stores.
[Woogy] By the way,
I think I'm gonna get a new car.
[Woogy] I'm young and rich now.
This car doesn't cut it anymore.
[car alarm beeps]
[exhales sharply]
[Woogy] Well anyway,
I'll be headed over there later.
You just, uh, bring the gold.
See you soon.
[exhales sharply]
[lightly chuckling]
[car alarm beeps]
[♪ suspenseful music]
YANGPO INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
[coughing]
[car alarm beeps]
[camera shutter clicks]
[door opens]
And who are you?
Oh, uh, hi.
Jeongsan Police Department.
Uh, Detective Kim Jinman.
Here's my business card for you.
[Yujin] The Jeongsan Police?
I thought that my team was cleared
of any involvement
and the investigation was over.
Yeah, sort of.
This particular case has become so complex
that we're conducting
a joint investigation.
And regarding Mr. Lee Dokyung,
we haven't caught the suspect
for the hit-and-run.
So the police still haven't been able
to find the casket?
-No, not yet.
-[Yujin] Hmm.
What do you want to ask me about, exactly?
You're close with Lee Dokyung, right?
You two call each other a lot?
Because of work, I guess.
There's nothing going on between us.
[exhales sharply]
It's been a while since we've talked.
So what's going on?
[inhales sharply]
I don't really know,
but I might need a favor.
[Yujin inhales on cigarette]
Could you get something through customs
for me?
[exhales]
Favor?
Why?
Why not just tell me you love me
like you used to?
[Yujin] You can't say it anymore?
You said it just fine
when you were cheating on me.
This is important.
I'm not playing around here.
[Jinman] You spoke with him on the phone
on the day of the accident, the fourth.
[exhales sharply]
Was I the only person who spoke
to Lee Dokyung that day?
[Jinman] Not at all.
Miss, this is just standard procedure.
I have to ask, 'kay?
Lee Dokyung, what did he say?
FIRST OFFICER LEE DOKYUNG:
THIS IS THE LAST TIME.
PLEASE JUST COME ONE MORE TIME TOMORROW.
I CAN GIVE YOU WHAT YOU REALLY WANT.
NATIONAL ROUTE 6, 50-7
[Yujin] We just talked
about personal stuff.
But I don't really feel like getting
into all that right now.
Oh.
So you're close enough to speak
about personal matters on the phone. Mm.
[Jinman] The day of the accident, then.
Do you happen to know anyone who
could verify where you were?
My alibi?
Your alibi, yeah.
You've already gone through
my call history.
STYLE
::cue()
Shouldn't you already know?
You see, the thing is,
we can't verify anything you did after
the call with Lee Dokyung.
At 10:00 p.m., you turned your phone off
for the rest of the night.
[Yujin] Well, I would have been home
at that time.
Mm-hmm.
Ah, wait.
I went to the theater that night.
For a late night movie.
Movie theater?
Which theater did you go to?
The theater in Sokcho.
Alone or with someone?
-I went alone.
-[Jinman] I see.
[groaning]
Do you happen to have anything that you
can show me like a ticket stub
or reservation E-mail that shows you
were there that night?
I'll be sure to look for it.
[Jinman] Yes, please do.
I'd appreciate that.
You know what?
[Jinman chuckles]
[Jinman] Whenever I question a suspect,
the most common alibi
is that they were at the theater.
If you had told me you were at home,
I could have confirmed with
the surveillance cameras pretty easily.
Unfortunately, the movie theaters
are trickier.
[Jinman] Did you drive to the theater?
-Well, no.
-[Jinman] Ah.
[Dokyung] It's not a big deal.
It's honestly nothing.
Just wait for my call and then bring
a van to the location I tell you.
That's all.
No.
[exhales]
Get out.
Do it yourself.
Don't even think about involving me.
It's a billion.
Is this what you meant
by giving me what I wanted?
Yujin! Are you listening?
Not a million.
It's a billion won.
Don't you think that amount
is worth betting on?
[Yujin] Betting?
Your whole life is just one big gamble.
No.
[Yujin] It just never ends with you.
There will always be more.
You'll keep doing this until it kills you.
[Yujin] But you don't get to ruin my life,
too, so get out.
[groans]
Yujin, we're so close. You can't-
don't-don't tell me
you're bailing out now!
[Yujin] Dokyung, this isn't fun anymore.
-What?
-[Yujin] Get out.
I said go.
[exhales sharply]
[car engine turns over]
-Am I a suspect?
-[Jinman] Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm just saying, it's quite a coincidence,
the whole theater thing. Yeah.
[Jinman] I get it, though.
[Jinman] Hmm.
So what's going to happen
to Lee Dokyung after all this?
[Jinman] Ah, well, he'll be transferred
to a detention center upon recovery
and then depending on
the outcome of his trial,
I'd say he'll likely serve
a year or two in prison.
I thought you told me you hadn't found
the casket yet.
[Yujin] If there's no evidence,
will he still go to jail?
No, but I'm sure we'll find
the casket soon. Yeah.
Oh.
[Jinman] Well, then,
I think that's just about everything
I wanted to ask you.
That means I need to speak
with Kim Heeju next.
So are you able to call her here for me,
or do I go somewhere else?
-Kim Heeju?
-Yeah.
Kim Heeju's alibi
hasn't been confirmed yet?
No, we haven't been able
to get a hold of her,
so her alibi is still unclear.
Heeju resigned recently.
She resigned? Why?
She said it was personal.
Oh.
Really?
TEAM LEADER
CHA YUJIN
If you can't reach her, I'll give her
a call and tell her to contact you, okay?
Ah, yeah, if you could do that,
I'd appreciate it.
Apologies for barging in earlier.
Yeah.
Did you buy that yourself?
No, it was a gift.
Gotcha.
Again, apologies for earlier.
Yeah.
STYLE
::cue()
[machines beeping]
What's going on with belt two?
[Heeju] It's all the metal decorations
attached to the casket.
Let it go through.
[machine rumbling]
[Yujin] He's gonna ask where you were
when Lee Dokyung had his accident.
Come up with an alibi.
[car horn honks]
Heeju!
[♪ ballad playing over stereo]
[Woogy grunts]
You bought a car?
I bought a new car.
Like it?
The sound is insane.
It's fucking surround sound!
[cheers]
Heeju, you should buy a car or something,
too.
[Woogy grunts]
We already paid the goldsmith one potato.
And I took four out of the 12
as my share.
[Woogy] And that's the rest.
[Woogy] 800 million.
We really did it.
I told you.
Heeju, have you ever seen so much cash?
[Woogy] Couldn't even imagine it!
It's crazy!
We're loaded now!
[Woogy laughing]
[inhales and exhales sharply]
That's one potato down.
Time for us to dig up the next one.
[car engine revving]
[shudders]
Oh, Cheoljung, it's me.
[Mija] How's your head feeling?
Are you okay?
I can't believe Sunok lost
her temper like that.
Let me see.
Good thing it isn't worse, right?
[Mija] Sunok came back
to her senses after she hurt you.
She called the police
and turned herself in.
I told you,
Sunok didn't do it.
[Mija] What do you mean?
She already told me everything.
[blade scraping]
You'll drop the charges, right?
[Mija] You wouldn't really send her
to jail, would you?
You know she has cancer.
She needs a hospital.
She wouldn't make it in a cold jail cell.
STYLE
::cue()
I beg you.
She is your wife.
[scoffs]
My wife?
That bitch was stealing my money.
And I doubt she'd care
if I was killed.
[knife scraping]
About that. Uh, she said she's planning
on returning it all to you.
[Mija] So if it's about the money,
don't worry bec-
Who said?
Who else? Sunok!
It's Heeju, huh?
Ah, no.
Why would you-Sunok, of course.
[Mija] She said she hasn't spent any
of the money yet.
I haven't seen Heeju in over five years.
Why are you suddenly asking about her?
[Cheoljung] Tell Heeju to bring
the money to me herself.
Got it?
Or I'll throw her in
the slammer with her aunt.
[gasping]
[blade scraping]
[cell phone vibrates]
[Mija] Heeju!
This is bad. We're fucked.
That bastard must have seen you.
He says you have to bring him
the money yourself
or he'll report you to the police!
You mean that asshole's still alive?
[Mija] Yes, he's still alive!
He got a few stitches but he survived
and now the bastard's awake.
And apparently he's filing
a police report.
I tried to convince him it wasn't you.
-I really tried.
-[Heeju] It's fine, Auntie.
-[Heeju] I'll take care of it.
-What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna go in there
and meet him face-to-face?
Or are you gonna turn yourself in
to the police?
Oh, it's not like your life
isn't fucked up enough already.
[Mija] Honestly, why is everyone
so hell-bent on screwing themselves over?
Shit!
[cell phone hangs up]
[Heeju exhales sharply]
What happened? Something wrong?
Who's the asshole?
Heeju.
We're partners now, aren't we?
Huh? We're supposed to talk to each other.
Your business is my business.
[Heeju] Do you actually believe that?
That my business is yours?
Of course.
Think about it.
If somethin' happens to you,
it'll screw up our business, hmm?
We only sold one potato.
There's plenty more to do.
[Woogy] I need you for that.
-[scream]
-[groans]
[thuds]
[breathing erratically]
[exhales sharply]
[Woogy] How come you won't just tell me?
I mean, who is it?
[Heeju exhales sharply]
[Woogy] You gonna answer?
STYLE
::cue()
[car alarm beeps]
[seat belt buckles]
[car engine turns over]
[tires squeak]
[♪ suspenseful music]
[car alarm beeps]
[groaning]
[Jinman] Shit.
[exhales sharply]
Pretty damn thorough.
NO DATA
[Jinman] She erased everything.
JEIL WORKSHOP
[blowtorch roaring]
[exhales sharply]
[Woogy] So, uh,
about the situation with your uncle.
I thought about what you told me.
Two options here.
First, give the bastard more money
than he asked for.
Then make him sign something
saying he'll never tell anyone.
Well, that's the first option, anyway.
[exhales sharply]
What's the second option?
[exhales]
I mean, I don't think you'll like it even
if I tell you,
because you're, like,
conscientious and all.
[exhales]
STYLE
::cue()
[smacks lips]
-[exhales]
-[Woogy] Don't worry.
You wouldn't have to do it yourself.
I'll do it for you.
And I'll clean it up, too.
Have you killed people before?
Well, I mean...
...for money, yeah.
I'll do anything for money.
For how much?
[inhales sharply]
Well, a one-kilo gold bar.
[Heeju exhales]
What about my aunt?
Is she trapped in jail?
I mean, if we-
if we get rid of him, then...
...she'd be released
'cause there's no real case.
Oh, wait.
Maybe she'd still have
to serve a year or two.
[Hoonseok clears throat]
How about this one?
[Hoonseok] This batch turned out great.
The bars are super smooth.
-Nice and shiny.
-[Woogy grunts]
[Woogy exhales]
[Woogy] Looks like you're getting better
and better each time.
[Woogy chuckles]
[Hoonseok chuckles]
[Woogy] Okay, back to work.
We're talking here.
[Hoonseok] Ah.
[Woogy exhales]
The first option is good.
Option one, then.
Not my money.
[Woogy inhales and exhales]
[keyboard clacking]
[♪ tense music]
JINGOGAE THREE-WAY INTERSECTION
[mouse wheel scrolling]
[Jinman] Looks like she was lying.
Just watching a movie?
Now I got you, lady.
CHA YUJIN
[groans]
[Gyeongsu yawns]
-[Jinman] Gyeongsu.
-Yeah?
[Jinman] I'm exhausted.
-[Gyeongsu] Well you've been working hard.
-[groans]
Oh, yeah.
That woman who hit her husband.
Was it attempted murder?
-Oh, Yeo Sunok?
-[Jinman] Yeah.
Where's she at?
She's in the holding cell.
-[Jinman exhales sharply]
-Why?
What's up with you?
Why are you still working so late?
The-the report isn't done yet.
Get back to it.
[Gyeongsu] Yeah.
STYLE
::cue()
-[Male Officer] Sir.
-[Jinman] Yeah.
Listen, I have a few questions
for the detainee.
Do you mind giving me the room just
for ten minutes?
[Male Officer] Of course, sir.
[keys jangling]
[lock clangs]
[door creaking]
[Jinman] Thanks.
-Come back in 10.
-[Male Officer] Yes, sir.
[Jinman] 'Kay.
[exhales]
[Jinman groaning and exhaling]
[scoffs]
[both scoffing]
[laughing]
Hey.
Of all the places we could have met, huh?
[inhales and exhales sharply]
[puffing]
[Jinman] Did you beat your husband
with a golf club?
Mm-hmm.
Why?
Just wanted the bastard dead.
[Jinman] Ah, that temper of yours.
If you say things like that in court,
they'll put you right in prison.
I don't care.
So what if they do?
It wouldn't even make that much
of a difference.
Your husband says it was 'cause of money.
[scoffs]
Well, that's part of it, too.
So this morning I overheard something.
You have cancer?
That true?
Seems like it.
Then stop smoking, Sunok.
Uh, here.
[Sunok exhales sharply]
You mean to settle?
No, I'll just go to prison, I think.
It sounds easier.
[door opens]
[Jinman] I'll go talk to your husband in
a couple of days.
Don't bother.
It doesn't matter.
[door creaks and clangs]
[keys jangling]
[door closes]
[glass bottle shatters]
[fist slams on table]
If you order a drink then shut up
and fucking drink it
-like a good little boy. You hear that?
-Oh, fuck you!
[all screaming]
[sirens blaring]
[tires screech]
[distant shouting]
GWIBIN COFFEE SHOP
[Man] The police, police!
[Police Partner] We're the police!
Break it up!
[Police Partner] Hey, hey!
[Woman] Don't push me!
[Police Partner] Come on!
That's enough. That's enough.
Hey, hey.
Just calm down.
-[Police Partner] Hey!
-[Woman] Leave her alone.
[all shouting]
-Put me down!
-[Woman] There he goes!
[exhales sharply]
Give me a light?
[lighter flicking]
[flame sizzles]
STYLE
::cue()
[gasps]
[Sunok] How come your hands are so pretty?
You play piano, officer?
Uh, no, ma'am.
[exhales]
[lighter flicking]
Guess it's true.
Men in uniform are pretty sexy.
[coughing]
[giggling]
Heeju!
[Cheoljung] You're here.
I was wondering when you'd show up.
Just look at you!
All grown up.
A real woman now.
I'm only here-I'm here to-
to return the money Auntie took from you.
What she stole?
Sure.
How much money?
100 million.
And how are you planning on returning it?
[Heeju] I can send it
to your bank account.
Or if you want I can give it
to you in cash.
[Cheoljung] Really?
Hmm.
Well, I want it back in cash.
[Heeju] Yes.
But before that...
...you have to drop
the charges against auntie.
Sure, no problem.
Then the three of us can live together.
We're family after all, aren't we?
No.
Auntie isn't doing very well.
It's cancer.
She might not live long.
So I want her to get treated.
In a hospital.
While there's still time
and she can live comfortably.
[Heeju] I'll stay by her side
while she's there.
But uncle...
...you're going to leave town
and not come back.
Why would I?
See, the thing is,
the house and the shop are here,
so where would I go?
[Heeju] You can sell the pawnshop to me.
I've already looked into it.
I know all about the loans and that
the shop is being used as collateral.
I'll take over your debts,
pay you the rest...
...and I'll even pay in cash.
How much?
How much do you want for it?
I won't sell it at market price. Hm.
Maybe for a billion won,
I'd let you have it.
Okay.
Seriously?
You got that kinda cash?
That much?
Yeah.
Is that so?
For that kind of money...
[Heeju] Come to the pawnshop
by 10:00 o'clock tonight.
I'll have the contract
and the money ready for you.
But first...
...you need to drop the charges.
Or the deal's off.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
STYLE
::cue()
[exhales sharply]
[grunts]
How did it go?
One billion to take his debt
and the store.
Ah, shit, that's crazy.
A billion won for that crumbling,
one-story building? Really?
-Drop me off at Yangpo Airport.
-[Woogy] Why?
I'm a bit short on cash.
How much more do you need?
I can have it ready
for you in just two days.
No, it has to be today.
I want to get my aunt out quickly.
[exhales sharply]
We're fucked. Shit.
Let me just lend it to you, okay?
CONFIRMATION OF SEVERANCE PAY RECEIPT
KIM HEEJU
[announcement chiming over speakers]
[Female Announcer] We will now
begin boarding.
I'll tell them to send it out immediately,
since it seems urgent.
Oh, thank you very much.
I appreciate it, Ms. Cha.
Where are you living nowadays, Heeju?
What?
I decided to take a look at your resume.
Your address and listed family are fake.
[Yujin] What exactly are you hiding?
-I'm staying with my aunt.
-[Yujin] Oh, really?
And where does your aunt live?
In Jeongsan.
Jeongsan?
[Jinman] Have you been to Jeongsan,
by any chance, recently?
-No.
-[Jinman] Okay.
You haven't then.
-Why are you asking?
-[Jinman inhales sharply]
[Jinman] Seems the smuggling
accomplice went
to Jeongsan with the casket.
[inhales]
There's no way.
You're the accomplice.
What?
Have you given your alibi?
Uh, no, not yet.
Okay, well...
...give the detective a call.
Do that first.
[Yujin] It might be best
to get ahead of it.
Just don't mention you're in Jeongsan,
because the thing is,
the police know that the van carrying
the casket went there.
[Yujin] Heeju, they're gonna find you.
It's only a matter of time.
I'm not sure I know
what you're talking about.
[exhales]
Okay.
Can't blame you, I guess.
Lee Dokyung is a bad guy.
[Yujin] Didn't I ever tell you?
No?
Lee Dokyung and I dated for a while.
[Yujin] Not anymore, though.
I was on National Route 6 that day, too.
He asked me to help him move the casket.
Obviously, I refused to help out.
You were clearly too blinded
by love, though.
[Yujin] It made you foolish.
He has as lover
in every location he flies to
STYLE
::cue()
I bet you didn't know that.
China, Hong Kong, Vietnam, Japan.
[Yujin] There are probably more here, too,
that we don't know about.
Do you think he actually loves
all those women?
Or are you telling yourself,
those relationships are all fake,
and you're the only one he truly loves?
[exhales]
I seriously don't know what you mean
by any of these things.
Ms. Cha, why are you telling me all this?
I'm trying to help you.
We're suspects.
As long as you're in the clear,
then I'm in the clear.
[Yujin] Lee Dokyung is just using you
and you keep letting him.
He's not worth it.
I wish you had just run off
with the casket yourself.
That would have been better.
[Yujin] But could you really hold out
on your own with the casket,
until Lee Dokyung gets outta jail?
Remember this, Heeju.
I'm the only person on your side now.
If something happens,
you should call me immediately.
[Yujin] I can help you out.
[inhales and exhales deeply]
What? Are they not gonna pay you?
Want me to take care of it?
No.
[cell phone vibrates]
[phone clicks]
[exhales]
THIS IS DETECTIVE KIM JINMAN.
PLEASE CALL ME WHEN YOU SEE THIS MESSAGE.
I'M CONTACTING YOU FOR A WITNESS
INTERVIEW. I HAVE A FEW THINGS TO ASK YOU.
-Ah, shit.
-[Woogy] What?
Who is it?
It's the police.
What?
What do they want?
Shit, did that fucker
Han Cheoljung report you?
No, the detective looking for the casket.
He suspects I helped Lee Dokyung.
Sounds like the police also know that
the van went to Jeongsan that day.
Ah, shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
[Woogy] What are you doing?
If I don't call him,
he'll suspect me more.
[exhales]
Hold on a sec.
STYLE
::cue()
Put it on speaker, okay?
[cell phone trilling]
[Jinman] This is Detective Kim Jinman
-of the Jeongsan Police.
-Uh...
...yes, hello.
You called because I used
to work at Yango Airport?
-This is Kim Heeju.
-Kim Jinman of Jeongsan?
[Jinman] Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Seems like Cha Yujin finally managed
to get a hold of you, then.
Anyway, well, I tried calling a bunch.
Then I stopped by your house
but you weren't there either.
I even went to Yangpo Airport
and they told me you left the company.
Is that right?
You no longer work there?
Uh, yeah, I've just been busy
with personal stuff so...
[Jinman] No worries.
Nothing major.
Just need to know where you were the day
of Lee Dokyung's accident.
The date was September fourth,
if you recall.
[Heeju] Uh, after I got off work...
...I remember I drove up to-
to Gangneung for the evening.
[Jinman] Gangneung?
And why go there?
You came all the way back
to work the next day.
[Heeju] Yeah, I just wanted
to clear my head,
so I went shopping
and then went to see a movie.
JEONGSAN POLICE STATION (INVESTIGATIONS
DIVISION) DETECTIVE KIM JINMAN
A movie, huh? On your own?
Yeah.
[Jinman] I see.
You don't have a car, right?
No.
[Jinman] Okay, I got it.
JEONGSAN POLICE STATION (INVESTIGATIONS
DIVISION) DETECTIVE KIM JINMAN
I'll be able to check
the rest on my end here.
All right, well,
thanks for calling.
Ooh.
Ah, shit!
Kim Jinman's with the company.
-He's a detective.
-Yeah, well, obviously.
But he's a detective who works with us.
Hey, Detective.
Doing okay?
[Woogy] Jeongsan Police,
Investigations Division, right?
That means it's not the fucking cops.
It's Yes Money chasing you.
They want to find their casket.
[Woogy] Ah, we're really fucked now.
[exhales sharply]
-Oh.
-Sir.
Uh, looks like the charges
are being dropped.
-O-open it. I need to talk to her.
-Yes, sir.
Thanks.
[keys rattling]
[Jinman] Ms. Yeo Sunok.
[door creaking]
Yeo Sunok.
What? Miss Yeo Sunok.
Hey, Yeo Sunok.
Sunok. Sunok! Wake up!
Hey, help me out here!
[Male Officer] Yes, sir.
[grunts]
[Jinman] Okay, call 911.
-Call them right now!
-[Male Officer] Yes, sir.
[distant sirens blaring]
[gasping]
[Mija whimpers]
[Mija] Sunok. Sunok, wake up.
Come on.
[Mija gasps]
What's wrong with her?
[Mija] Doc-doctor!
[gasps]
No!
Sunok, no!
Sunok, please, open your eyes!
[Mija crying]
[Mija] Sunok!
Please!
[crying]
[Mija] They said she got blood
in her lungs and went into shock.
Oh, so stupid.
She could have asked them
to take her to the hospital.
But instead she just sat there suffering
with a hole in her lung.
Like she wanted to die.
So, what did you say to your uncle?
He dropped the charges.
How did you manage that?
[inhales deeply]
Will you please do me a favor
and stay with her tonight?
I'll be there tomorrow.
[inhales]
[groans]
Tonight? It's Friday, though.
[grunts]
I'm supposed to be working tonight.
[exhales]
I-I'll pay you a million won
for your trouble.
[Mija] Okay, okay.
I'm sorry, auntie.
Thank you.
[phone beeps]
[inhales and exhales sharply]
Heeju.
Let's take a sec to think about it.
About what?
[Woogy] About shutting Han Cheoljung up
with hush money.
How can you be sure?
That asshole could still
rat you out after.
The second he gives your name
to the police,
Detective Kim will find out, too.
That means he'll know without
a doubt you went to Jeongsan.
[exhales sharply]
But he did get my aunt out
like he promised.
Exactly.
So you don't have
to worry about her anymore.
STYLE
::cue()
Didn't you say you wanted him dead?
[Woogy] Heeju.
You think it'll end here?
Not a chance.
[Woogy] I know assholes
like him too damn well.
He'll keep coming back,
asking for money again and again.
[Woogy] As long as you and your aunt
are still here,
he'll never leave you alone.
Why put yourself in such
a dangerous situation?
And if Detective Kim catches you...
...then it'll all be over, Heeju.
The gold bars.
Everything.
HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
Haengbok Pawnshop, huh?
[door creaks]
[Cheoljung] Heeju!
Read it over.
So, the money.
Where is it?
I wanna see it myself first.
[exhales]
[grunting]
[Heeju grunts]
[zipper unzips]
[Cheoljung gasping]
I didn't believe you!
What the...
...what the hell have you been doing
all these years, Heeju?
[Cheoljung] I mean, how could you
possibly have this kind of money?
Sign the contract.
Uh, okay.
Yeah, sure.
[zipper zipping]
[exhales]
You know I can't do it, Heeju.
[Cheoljung] Let's stop
and think this over again, okay?
[Cheoljung] Who cares
who owns the pawnshop?
That doesn't matter.
Family is all that matters.
You and me, your aunt,
we should all live together.
Sign the contract.
I'm not telling you again.
[Cheoljun] The whole drive here,
I put a lotta thought into this.
[inhales and exhales sharply]
Your poor aunt.
[Cheoljung] She has cancer
and not much time to live.
I just think while she's alive,
she'd be happier if we were all together.
We're supposed to be family.
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
-Family?
-[Cheoljung] If we weren't family,
I would've reported you
to the police right away, ya know?
[Cheoljung] You swung that club at me.
I saw your face as clear as day.
[Cheoljung] Or would you rather I go
to the police right now
and let 'em know it was you?
[Heeju grunts]
What should I spend all this money on?
Pay off the loan?
Well, seeing as it is our store,
let's do that.
Oh, sweetie, being on your own
was so hard wasn't it?
No. No! No! No!
-[grunting]
-Ah, shit.
[grunting]
[Cheoljung grunts]
[slaps]
[Heeju wails]
Ah, you little shit.
[Heeju groaning]
[groaning]
[Cheoljung] Don't even think
about leaving.
Just stay here
and look after the pawnshop.
[Cheoljung] While your aunt dies.
[snickers]
[coughing]
[Heeju gasping]
Goodbye.
[groaning and gasping]
[Heeju] Woogy!
[door creaking]
[door lock clicks]
Bastard, who are you?
[groaning]
Evil son of a bitch.
STYLE
::cue()
Should I do it?
[clock ticking echoes]
Yeah.
Do it.
[both grunting]
[blade slices]
[both shouting]
[pained gasping]
[both grunting]
[blade slicing]
[blade piercing]
[gagging and sputtering]
[blood squelching]
[Woogy breathing heavily]
[♪ dramatic music]
[blade clatters]
[both breathing heavily]
[♪ music continues]